export const CricketQuiz = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which team has won most number of icc trophies`,
    option1: `India`,
    option2: `Australia`,
    option3: `West Indies`,
    option4: `England`,
    answer: `Australian`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which player holds the record for most number of sixes in international crrciket`,
    option1: `Shahid Afridi`,
    option2: `Rohit Sharma`,
    option3: `Brandon McCullum`,
    option4: `Chris Gayle`,
    answer: `Chris Gayle`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which team has won the most number of ipl trophies`,
    option1: `Chennai Super Kings`,
    option2: `Royal Challengers Bangalore`,
    option3: `Mumbai Indians`,
    option4: `Kolkata Knight Riders`,
    answer: `Mumbai Indians`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which player holds the rcord for most number of international wicket`,
    option1: `M Muralitharan`,
    option2: `Wasim Akram`,
    option3: `Shane Warne`,
    option4: `A Kumble`,
    answer: `M Muralitharan`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Who was the first player to score a odi double hundred`,
    option1: `Rohit Sharma`,
    option2: `Virender Sehwag`,
    option3: `Sachin Tendulkar`,
    option4: `Chris Gayle`,
    answer: `Sachin Tendulkar`,
  },
];

export const CapitalQuiz = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is the capital of China`,
    option1: `Wuhan`,
    option2: `Beijing`,
    option3: `Hainan`,
    option4: `Yunnan`,
    answer: `Beijing`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is the capital of Australia`,
    option1: `Melbourne`,
    option2: `Sydney`,
    option3: `Brisbane`,
    option4: `Canberra`,
    answer: `Canberra`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is the capital of UAE`,
    option1: `Abu Dhabi`,
    option2: `Dubai`,
    option3: `Sharjah`,
    option4: `New Delhi`,
    answer: `Abu Dhabi`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is the capital of Japan`,
    option1: `Kyoto`,
    option2: `Heroshima`,
    option3: `Tokyo`,
    option4: `Nagoya`,
    answer: `Tokyo`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is the capital of India`,
    option1: `News Delhi`,
    option2: `Jaipur`,
    option3: `Rajasthan`,
    option4: `Uttar Pradesh`,
    answer: `New Delhi`,
  },
];

export const BollywoodQuiz = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What was the name of villain in Sholay movie`,
    option1: `Shakaal`,
    option2: `Kalia`,
    option3: `Gabbar Singh`,
    option4: `Bulla`,
    answer: `Gabbar Singh`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Name of female lead character in DDLJ`,
    option1: `Simran`,
    option2: `Senorita`,
    option3: `Paro`,
    option4: `Shalu`,
    answer: `Simran`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Finish the quote from Deewar: "Mere Paas _____ hai?"`,
    option1: `Paisa`,
    option2: `Iphone`,
    option3: `Maa`,
    option4: `Daad, Khaj, Khujli`,
    answer: `Maa`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Real name of Rancho in 3 idiots movie`,
    option1: `Ranchhoddas Shamaldas Chanchad`,
    option2: `Chatur Ramalingam`,
    option3: `Phunsukh Wangdu`,
    option4: `Virus`,
    answer: `Ranchhoddas Shamaldas Chanchad`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `In "Chak De India" how many minutes, cording to coach Kabir Khan, doest the team have?`,
    option1: `30`,
    option2: `35`,
    option3: `10`,
    option4: `70`,
    answer: `70`,
  },
];

export const FootballQuiz = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which of the following country won footbll world cup maximum time?`,
    option1: `Germany`,
    option2: `Italy`,
    option3: `Argentina`,
    option4: `Brazil`,
    answer: `Brazil`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Who among the following players have scored maximum number of goals in World Cup?`,
    option1: `Jurgen Kinsmann`,
    option2: `Meradona`,
    option3: `Miroslave Klose`,
    option4: `Pele`,
    answer: `Miroslave Klose`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which of the following term is recognised as an early form of football by FIFA?"`,
    option1: `Kemari`,
    option2: `Episkyros`,
    option3: `Cuju`,
    option4: `Inuit`,
    answer: `Episkyros`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `When was the first FIFA World Cup inaugurated?`,
    option1: `1930`,
    option2: `1931`,
    option3: `1932`,
    option4: `1933`,
    answer: `1930`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which of following team do not play in stripes`,
    option1: `Newcastle`,
    option2: `Tottenham Hotspur`,
    option3: `Southampton`,
    option4: `Lincoln City`,
    answer: `Tottenham Hotspur`,
  },
];

export const HockeyQuiz = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which among these is the highest governing body of Hockey?`,
    option1: `International Hockey Federation`,
    option2: `World Hockey Federation`,
    option3: `Federation of International Hockey`,
    option4: `International Hockey Association`,
    answer: `International Hockey Federation`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: ` Total no. of players playing on the pitch in a hockey match is?`,
    option1: `22`,
    option2: `16`,
    option3: `20`,
    option4: `18`,
    answer: `22`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which player is allowed to touch the ball with his feet during a Hockey match?`,
    option1: `Defender`,
    option2: `Centre-forward`,
    option3: `Winger`,
    option4: `Goalkeeper`,
    answer: `Goalkeeper`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `The dimensions of a Hockey field are?`,
    option1: `92m X 56m`,
    option2: `90m X 50m`,
    option3: `92m X 55m`,
    option4: `91.4m X 55m`,
    answer: `91.4m X 55m`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: ` The distance between thepenalty spot and the goal is?`,
    option1: `6 yards`,
    option2: `5 yards`,
    option3: `8 yards`,
    option4: `7 yards`,
    answer: `7 yards`,
  },
];

export const WweQuiz = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is Brock Lesnar's Finisher name?`,
    option1: `AA`,
    option2: `F5`,
    option3: `Pedigree`,
    option4: `STF`,
    answer: `F5`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which wrestler is famous for RKO finisher`,
    option1: `Randy Orton`,
    option2: `Umaga`,
    option3: `HHH`,
    option4: `Kane`,
    answer: `Randy Orton`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Who Did Undertaker Lose Too At Wrestlemania 30`,
    option1: `Bray Wyatt`,
    option2: `Brock Lesnar`,
    option3: `John Cena`,
    option4: `The Rock`,
    answer: `Brock Lesnar`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Which wrestler is knwon for 619 move`,
    option1: `Rey Mesterio`,
    option2: `Khali`,
    option3: `Batista`,
    option4: `Kane`,
    answer: `Rey Mesterio`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What was former name of StarDust`,
    option1: `Codey Rhodes`,
    option2: `Rey Mesterio`,
    option3: `John Mohrassen`,
    option4: `Sin Cara`,
    answer: `Codey Rhodes`,
  },
];
